We're taking you with us to walk the Stations
of the Cross in Lourdes.  So this morning, we got up
at 8am with Keetana.  Look,
I have a bag full of souvenirs.
Keaetana, she was so looking forward to
this ordeal, I swear.
Heet?
Yeah.  Yeah.
Plus, today we don't have the support,
so frankly, we're super happy.
It was absolutely beautiful.
I swear, this Stations of the Cross is
so beautiful.  Keitana told me,
"Mom, it's just magnificent."  I'm
filming a few short sections of the Stations of the
Cross.  Afterwards, we visited
Bernadette Sirou's house.
Honestly, it's magnificent.  Kaitana
loved it.  We bought lots of
souvenirs.  Let me know in the comments
if you would like a hall of our memories
in Lourdes.  And now we're going to wait until 1:45 pm
because Kaitana absolutely wants to
visit the wax museum.  It
took us about 40 minutes to do the Stations of the Cross
.  Are we talking
about beauty?  But look, it's
simply magnificent.  Kaana bought a
small rose, so she's going to put it down.
I am so proud of my daughter,
you can't imagine.  So we
continue.  We walk.  We walk.
Honestly, it feels so good.
After that, we're going to sit down with Keitana and have
a bite to eat.  Afterwards, we'll
go to the cave to light our torches.
We bought small jicans to
fill with obenity.
I hope you enjoyed this ordeal with
you.  Anyway, we'll
leave you to it.  We send you lots of
kisses and above all, take care of yourselves.
Mr.